A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor John Letcher, 1859-1863
Library of Virginia
- Chronological Files, 1859-1863, 13.45 cu. ft.
  - Correspondence, 1-31 October 1863 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Pardons, 1-23 October 1863 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Pardons, 24-31 October 1863 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2-30 November 1863 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pardons, 2-9 November 1863 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pardons, 10-28 November 1863 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1-31 December 1863 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Pardons, December 1863 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Pardons -- Adams, Notley P., December 1863 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Pardons -- Adams, Notley P., December 1863 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Pardons -- Adams, Notley P., December 1863 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, undated 1863 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Undated correspondence, part 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Undated correspondence, part 2 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Subject Files, 1860-1861, .9 cu. ft.
  The Subject files series (1860-1861) consists of three different subjects: the Advisory Council, John Brown's Raid, and Railroads.
  - Advisory Council
    - Correspondence, April 1861 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1-10 May 1861 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 11-20 May 1861 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 21-27 May 1861 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 28-31 May 1861 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, June 1861 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - List of Applicants for Commissions, April 1860 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings, April-May 1861 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings, June 1861 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings - Advice of the Council relative to Captured Machinery, Ordnance, etc., May-June 1861 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings - Advice of the Council relative to the Transfer of Troops and Public Property to the Confederate States, April-June 1861 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Reports from Committees, January-March 1861 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - John Brown's Raid
    - General, January-March 1860 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - General, April-December 1860 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Detectives, 1860-1861 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Stuart, J.E.B., 1860 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Expenses - General, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Expenses - Hospital and Sick, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Expenses - Payrolls, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Expenses - Purchase of Arms, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Expenses - Quarter Master, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Railroads
    - Reports from the Committee on Railroad Connections, June 1861 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Richmond and Danville Railroad, June 1861 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad, May-June 1861 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Winchester and Potomac Railroad, April 1861 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Oversized, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Oversized, 1861 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Oversized, 1862-1863 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Oversized, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Oversized - John Brown's Raid, 1860 (Box 32, Folder 5)